[
  { "question": "نيريا",      "response": "ايرين" },
  { "question": "يافيل",      "response": "ليفاي" },
  { "question": "اساكيم",     "response": "ميكاسا" },
  { "question": "نمرا",       "response": "ارمين" },
  { "question": "ايروتسهي",   "response": "هيستوريا" },
  { "question": "رينيار",     "response": "راينر" },

  { "question": "يفول",       "response": "لوفي" },
  { "question": "ورزو",       "response": "زورو" },
  { "question": "يجناس",      "response": "سانجي" },
  { "question": "ايمان",      "response": "نامي" },
  { "question": "بوسوا",      "response": "اوسوب" },
  { "question": "نيبور",      "response": "روبن" },

  { "question": "وتوران",     "response": "ناروتو" },
  { "question": "يكساس",      "response": "ساسكي" },
  { "question": "اركاس",      "response": "ساكورا" },
  { "question": "يشاك اك",    "response": "كاكاشي" },
  { "question": "يشاتيا",     "response": "ايتاشي" },
  { "question": "ارادام",     "response": "مادارا" },

  { "question": "وكوغ",       "response": "غوكو" },
  { "question": "اتيجيف",     "response": "فيجيتا" },
  { "question": "ناهوغ",      "response": "غوهان" },
  { "question": "ولكيب",      "response": "بيكولو" },
  { "question": "ازيرف",      "response": "فريزا" },
  { "question": "سكنارت",     "response": "ترانكس" },

  { "question": "وغيشيا",     "response": "ايشيغو" },
  { "question": "ايكور",      "response": "روكيا" },
  { "question": "يميهيرو",    "response": "اوريهيمي" },
  { "question": "ويروا",      "response": "اوريو" },
  { "question": "داشت",       "response": "تشاد" },
  { "question": "ايوكايب",    "response": "بياكويا" },

  { "question": "ايوريدم",    "response": "ميدوريا" },
  { "question": "وغوكاب",     "response": "باكوغو" },
  { "question": "يكورودوت",   "response": "تودوروكي" },
  { "question": "تيام للا",   "response": "ال مايت" },
  { "question": "اكاراروا",   "response": "اوراراكا" },
  { "question": "اديي",       "response": "اييدا" },

  { "question": "اوريجنات",   "response": "تانجيرو" },
  { "question": "وكزين",      "response": "نيزوكو" },
  { "question": "وتسينيز",    "response": "زينيتسو" },
  { "question": "يكسونيا",    "response": "اينوسكي" },
  { "question": "ويغ",        "response": "غيو" },
  { "question": "وبونيش",     "response": "شينوبو" },

  { "question": "يروداتيا",   "response": "ايتادوري" },
  { "question": "وروغيشوف",   "response": "فوشيغورو" },
  { "question": "وجوغ",       "response": "غوجو" },
  { "question": "ارابون",     "response": "نوبارا" },
  { "question": "يموغيم",     "response": "ميغومي" },
  { "question": "وتيهام",     "response": "ماهيتو" },

  { "question": "يكيناك",     "response": "كانيكي" },
  { "question": "اكوت",       "response": "توكا" },
  { "question": "يديه",       "response": "هيدي" },
  { "question": "امايوكست",   "response": "تسوكياما" },
  { "question": "وزوج",       "response": "جوزو" },
  { "question": "اتوا",       "response": "اوتا" },

  { "question": "كوير",       "response": "ريوك" },
  { "question": "اسيم",       "response": "ميسا" },
  { "question": "راين",       "response": "نير" },
  { "question": "وليم",       "response": "ميلو" },
  { "question": "ادستام",     "response": "ماتسودا" },
  { "question": "يراتاوا",    "response": "واتاري" },

  { "question": "دراودا",     "response": "ادوارد" },
  { "question": "سنوفلا",     "response": "الفونس" },
  { "question": "يرنيو",      "response": "وينري" },
  { "question": "غتنسم",      "response": "مستنغ" },
  { "question": "زغوه",       "response": "هوغز" },
  { "question": "غنورتسمرا",  "response": "ارمسترونغ" },

  { "question": "نوغ",        "response": "غون" },
  { "question": "اوليك",      "response": "كيلوا" },
  { "question": "اكاباروك",   "response": "كورابيكا" },
  { "question": "ويرول",      "response": "ليوريو" },
  { "question": "اكوسيه",     "response": "هيسوكا" },
  { "question": "ولوروك",     "response": "كورولو" },

  { "question": "وستان",      "response": "ناتسو" },
  { "question": "يسول",       "response": "لوسي" },
  { "question": "يارغ",       "response": "غراي" },
  { "question": "ازريأ",      "response": "ايرزا" },
  { "question": "يدنيو",      "response": "ويندي" },
  { "question": "ليجاغ",      "response": "غاجيل" },

  { "question": "اتسأ",       "response": "استا" },
  { "question": "اونـي",      "response": "يونو" },
  { "question": "ليون",       "response": "نويل" },
  { "question": "يماي",       "response": "يامي" },
  { "question": "تلراش",      "response": "شارلوت" },
  { "question": "نويولوغيف",  "response": "فويغوليون" },

  { "question": "يكوتنج",     "response": "جينتوكي" },
  { "question": "ارستاك",     "response": "كاتسورا" },
  { "question": "يحشابنش",    "response": "شينباتشي" },
  { "question": "اتاكيجيه",   "response": "هيجيكاتا" },
  { "question": "اتيكوا",     "response": "اوكيتا" },
  { "question": "وغوس",       "response": "سوغو" },

  { "question": "ناثانوج",    "response": "جوناثان" },
  { "question": "فيسوج",      "response": "جوزيف" },
  { "question": "اوراتوج",    "response": "جوتارو" },
  { "question": "يكسوج",      "response": "جوسكي" },
  { "question": "ونروج",      "response": "جورنو" },
  { "question": "ويد",        "response": "ديو" },

  { "question": "شتوليل",     "response": "ليلوتش" },
  { "question": "وكازوس",     "response": "سوزاكو" },
  { "question": "نلاك",       "response": "كالين" },
  { "question": "ايميفوي",    "response": "يوفيميا" },
  { "question": "ايلينروك",   "response": "كورنيليا" },
  { "question": "ايماريرج",   "response": "جيريمايا" },

  { "question": "وتيريك",     "response": "كيريتو" },
  { "question": "انوسا",      "response": "اسونا" },
  { "question": "نونيس",      "response": "سينون" },
  { "question": "افيل",       "response": "ليفا" },
  { "question": "وجيؤ",       "response": "يوجيو" },
  { "question": "سيلا",       "response": "اليس" },

  { "question": "اتانيه",     "response": "هيناتا" },
  { "question": "امايايغاك",  "response": "كاغياما" },
  { "question": "ويبوت",      "response": "توبيو" },
  { "question": "ايونيهشن",   "response": "نيشينوا" },
  { "question": "اكانات",     "response": "تاناكا" },
  { "question": "يشياد",      "response": "دايشي" },

  { "question": "ورابوس",     "response": "سوبارو" },
  { "question": "ايلميا",     "response": "ايميليا" },
  { "question": "مير",        "response": "ريم" },
  { "question": "مار",        "response": "رام" },
  { "question": "سيرتعيب",    "response": "بياتريس" },
  { "question": "لاوسور",     "response": "روسوال" },

  { "question": "سادويلوم",   "response": "ميليوداس" },
  { "question": "تهبازللاي",  "response": "اليزابيث" },
  { "question": "ناب",        "response": "بان" },
  { "question": "غنيك",       "response": "كنغ" },
  { "question": "رهيتوغ",     "response": "غوثر" },
  { "question": "روناكسيا",   "response": "ايسكانور" },

  { "question": "وريش",       "response": "شيرو" },
  { "question": "رباس",       "response": "سابر" },
  { "question": "نير",        "response": "رين" },
  { "question": "رشترا",      "response": "ارتشر" },
  { "question": "هسامجليج",   "response": "جلجامش" },
  { "question": "رتساك",      "response": "كاستر" },

  { "question": "اماتياس",    "response": "سايتاما" },
  { "question": "سونيج",      "response": "جينوس" },
  { "question": "يكاموستات",  "response": "تاتسوماكي" },
  { "question": "يكوبوف",     "response": "فوبوكي" },
  { "question": "سينوس",      "response": "سونيك" },
  { "question": "وراغ",       "response": "غارو" },

  { "question": "نانوك",      "response": "كونان" },
  { "question": "نار",        "response": "ران" },
  { "question": "يحشينيش",    "response": "شينيتشي" },
  { "question": "وروقوك",     "response": "كوغورو" },
  { "question": "يجيه",       "response": "هيجي" },
  { "question": "يا",         "response": "اي" },

  { "question": "ستوغ",       "response": "غاتس" },
  { "question": "هيتيفيرغ",   "response": "غريفيث" },
  { "question": "اكساك",      "response": "كاسكا" },
  { "question": "ايسنراف",    "response": "فارنيز" },
  { "question": "وكيفرس",     "response": "سيربيكو" },
  { "question": "يكريهش",     "response": "شيركه" }
]
